Hello there!
Howdy!
I'm Hatake, Noko Hatake.
Oh, but everyone calls
me field these days.
I was just a regular old student in Japan,
then all of a sudden,
that anime thing happened.
I was reborn in another world,
as a field of all things.
I'm 100 meters long on each
side and 10 meters deep.
Now then, let me introduce
you to my lovable family.
See that sleek fellow with black
feathers, three eyes, and three legs?
That's Kuroyata, the ruler of the skies.
The party animal with a cute horn who
loves rushing into danger. Bow time!
A sluffle of sharp ears and fuzzy faces.
Meet the dad, Usata.
Mama Usarion and kiddos,
Usarion and Usapi.
That's my fam for ya.
But wait, there's more!
This grateful ground has close pals.
Kikuyu, the recently grown-up snow fairy.
I mean, we're so close,
she's basically family.
She's my interpreter,
so I owe her big time.
And someone whose captivating eyes
almost made me accidentally fall in love.
The lovely head of the fortified city
with a truly bewitching gaze, Jessica.
He's sharp as a tack and looks
like a standard-issue butler.
Stick.
Expressionless, potty-mouthed,
and so gosh-darn fond of animals,
she has a tendency to gush over
them to an uncomfortable degree.
It's murder.
She dresses like a knight,
but she's actually a princess.
Though she seems like
the epitome of capable,
she's more of a hot mess than you think.
It's Hayachi.
Qyoehkotek is the vampire
necromancer with an impossible
name who runs hot and cold
and is the left-leg general.
Those awesome peeps are my support system.
Thanks to them, my time as a sentient field
has been peaceful and pleasantly boring.
Oh, except for that one time I
fought the Demon Lord's army.
After a fierce duel with the Demon
Lord's former left-legged general,
my consciousness was interrupted, and
I lost my sense of self for a while.
The days melted away as I
drifted through darkness.
I nearly went mad from the loneliness,
until one day, out of nowhere,
the light returned.
The darkness was gone, replaced by my
friends and family in a world of light.
Actually, that was just a few weeks ago.
While I was spiraling into madness,
Qyoehkotek was spreading my top-tier
veggie seeds and seedlings around.
That fixed the little starvation issue
plaguing the Demon Lord's domain.
This made the Demon Lord pro-field,
and I was soon invited to his
castle so we could begin peace
negotiations between his Demon
forces and the fortified city.
Shui, now you're up to speed.
Silly field, you've been monologuing
for almost three minutes straight.
Whatever am I going to do with you?
Kiku, you!
I can't believe you've blossomed
into such a beauty queen!
That's sweet of you to say, though I'm
unaccustomed to receiving such compliments.
Piece, I totally forgot.
She can hear my innermost thoughts.
What's with all the
shameless flirting over here?
And more importantly, why
isn't any of it directed at me?
Qyoehkotek.
Even though she saved the
demon realm from famine
and became the new
left-legged general to boot,
that overachiever still spends
her days tending to my gardens.
But on a positive note, you've really
gotten the hang of moving around.
I can hardly feel the
ground shaking anymore.
You're doing so much better now.
Thanks!
I've been practicing.
These fieldy feet are taking
us to the demon lord's castle!
Whaaaaaa!
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box.
But inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner, Lamas!
The name's Boxxo. Hello there!
That means yes, by the way.
Take my turn.
Go, go, go!
How do you feel?
God, no, that's me.
I'm beyond stoked to visit
the Demon Lord's castle.
He's a surprisingly decent person.
We've spoken a handful
of times at this point.
I kind of like the guy.
The sun barely shines in the Demon Realm.
It's a barren place
where crops won't grow.
Till now, I've been working
my bountiful booty off.
To modify the veggies I produce?
into hardy, drought-resistant cultivars.
They're spreading like wildfire
around the demon realm,
making mincemeat of that
nasty food shortage.
Now that we're not desperate for
resources, we've even stopped warmongering.
A happy side effect is that
everyone in the demon realm
has been treating me like
some kind of heroic hotshot.
Me, a humble field!
You know I don't like it
when you're overly modest.
Why shouldn't everyone be in awe of the
person who made those
life-saving vegetables?
You're so nice, Kikuyu.
By the way, I was hoping
you could tell me?
About that other Japanese guy you met?
who was reborn as an inanimate
object in this world.
Sure, I'd be happy to.
Wild.
What are the odds that another Japanese
dude would be reincarnated here?
He was reborn as a vending machine and
now wanders the dungeon. Righteous!
That's even random by anime standards!
Er, says I, the guy who
was reborn as a field.
That's right.
I clearly remember him saying
he was a vending machine.
He has the ability to transform
into different types of
vending machine at will and
dispense the associated products.
It sounds like he helped
you out of a ripe pickle.
So once we settle our problems here, I'm
thinking we should go and return the favor.
You know,
I still can't believe the left-armed
general's been plotting in the dungeon.
Don't worry.
No matter what happens, I'm
staying right by your side.
There's just one little problem.
Can I ask Qyoehkotek for help when
she's the new left-legged general?
Guess I'll have to shoot my
shot and see what happens.
No stalling.
It's now or never.
Yeah, of course I'll stick around.
The Demon Lord is ultimately just my boss.
I haven't forgotten, you're the one who
saved my village in this entire realm.
But don't get the wrong idea.
It's not like I have a secret
crush on you or anything.
I'm just paying you back, that's all.
I love a good tsundere trope.
But in all seriousness,
I'll assume she's being honest about
not crushing on a large clump of dirt.
I'll just count myself lucky
to have such a reliable ally.
Her ability to control the
dead is necromantastic,
and the two of us have amazing chemistry.
If you want good
chemistry, look no further.
True, it do be that way.
It's the Demon Lord's castle.
The head honcho, looking
effortlessly suave as always.
He's buff and handsome,
not to mention charismatic.
On paper, it looks like
an overwhelming defeat.
Not today, demon lord.
Those buff arms can't produce
life-saving sustenance. See that?
I'm not even a tiny bit jealous.
Alrighty, got that out of my system.
That elder gent is the
right-armed general.
He strikes me as a dandy who's
50 but still fit as a fiddle.
If I'd continued aging like a
human, I'd probably look similar.
Who am I kidding?
I didn't even look that good in my prime.
Pardon me for literally treading on you.
It's finally time for the moment of truth.
Here's hoping our peace
negotiations go as expected.
I have not seen you in a long while
Or you, my faithful left-legged
general It's good to see you, sire
Long time Yes,
too long And drop the formalities,
Qyoehkotek Right, general?
Since our realm of Lord
Fiela did have gratitude.
It seems he deserves an exception.
Oh.
By the way.
I feel a bit dehydrated.
I wish I could wet my tongue
with something refreshing.
I know exactly what he wants,
and I know, he knows, I know.
Please help yourself.
Today's juice.
It's from freshly squeezed Barrens.
Lovely. I accept.
My lord!
Was it poisoned?
Calm yourself.
It was so delectable, I felt woozy.
You simply must have a swig. Enjoy!
Impressive recovery!
You've earned yourself a little treat!
Oh, so shiny! Ha!
Even the Demon Lord is no
match for a juicy fruit basket!
You're in good spirits.
Having fun?
Yep, I'm living my best life. Mm.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha! Incredible!
It's possible I overdid it on the umami.
Wanna save peace talks for tomorrow?
No, I'd like to get this done today.
There!
Now the Demon Lord's army will finally
stop attacking the fortified city.
Oh, Usapi and Usarion!
Do you have something for me in there?
This is unexpected.
I thought the Usapta family was off
investigating the murderous forest with Hayachi.
Let's see.
The left-armed general is...
That fiend is pulling shenanigans
during pace negotiations!
You seem perturbed.
Interesting.
He stole the dungeon's power and now
he's marching on the fortified city.
See this?
Well now, the left-armed general
really outdid himself this time.
Was this on your orders?
Of course it wasn't.
That wayward general did
this of his own volition.
I've known that he was capable
of treachery for a while now,
but attaining the dungeon's
power must have gone to his head.
Then it's no problem if I
crush him? Left arm? Do it.
I don't mind.
I'll even send reinforcements
to help you out.
If I may, I would like
to undertake that duty.
That's what I had in
mind as well. Go ahead.
Sire, I won't fail you.
We wrote a letter about
friending up the Demon Lord,
and then gave it to Kuroyata to
deliver it to the fortified city.
We left the Demon Lord's realm and should
be reaching the city
ourselves before long.
Okay,
once we make it there, I'll have to request
to speak with Lady Jessica post-haste.
It's just,
the moment we lock eyes, I might go
into a trance and forget why I'm there!
You seem especially giddy when you
speak with Lady Jessica, am I wrong?
That observation is accurate.
who doesn't act that way in my presence.
I don't have the foggiest idea
what you're talking about.
The ladies in my life are
having a House fit. The cure?
Some fresh Utsugas.
Hey, you can't buy our
forgiveness, so don't even try it.
Yeah, she's right.
You can't tempt a woman with
fruit, you snake. Come on, now.
You know you want some of this.
You can't fool me, ladies.
Give in to temptation.
Field, stop being so creepy. Creepy?
What was that dirtbag thinking?
I'll tell you.
A few stray thoughts and
they're teaming up against me.
We love real!
Welcome back, Guardian.
It's lovely to see you.
Good to be back.
I'm glad you seem to be thriving.
I'm supposed to be a field,
not an active volcano!
Be strong.
Jessica's a dude.
A bodacious dude.
But my brain must master my hormones!
I'll just say this once.
You're making Field uncomfortable.
Please take your hands off him at once.
Are you truly uncomfortable,
my precious guardian?
Is it really so wrong for
me to stroke you like this?
I may be afield, but I'm still a man.
I can't say yes when those
dazzling eyes are staring at me.
Welp, I guess I'll plead the fifth.
Answer already. You're waiting.
It makes you uncomfortable,
doesn't it, field?
Yay, yay!
The path of retreat has been blockaded!
Requesting immediate backup!
Dang, looks like I'm on my own.
Alright, let's clear things up, shall we?
If you had to decide between the
three of us, who would you choose?
That's a rather intriguing proposition.
I have absolutely no
romantic interest in you,
but if you insist on being with me,
I'll give it serious consideration.
No promises.
If you choose me, I swear I'll
devote my life to making you happy.
Whoa!
Quick reminder, I'm a field?
Last time I checked, fields
don't have harem battles?
Answer.
Did you all forget your crazy pills?
I'm a field! Pack dirt! Whip chow! Answer!
Emergency Destruction!
These babies are all yours if you help me
think of a plan to be
the Left Arm General.
So be it.
We shall indulge in those
Utsukas after our War Council.
Agreed.
Looks like I narrowly
avoided disaster. But wait!
The fortified city's under attack!
So shouldn't we have started
the War Council ASAP?
Is this charade finally over?
If you're finished, we should
begin the War Council at once.
We're fast approaching the final showdown!
Woo-wee!
Getting to fill up our bellies with piping
out food on the
battlefield's a real luxury!
It truly is.
Hey, Hulemy!
You should eat something!
Just as soon as I finish installing this.
Hulamy's upgrading the Cap's wagon so
we can hitch it to my pimped-out pickup.
As the saying goes, waste not, want not.
It just had to rain, didn't it?
I was almost finished, too.
Rain, I'm afraid you've met your match.
Behold the glory of
poncho vending machines.
They're for water rides in theme parks.
This is perfect, Boxo.
We built a shelter from
the concrete blocks I
can plop out when I'm a
giant vending machine.
The injured hunters can rest there
safely while we rush to find our friends.
There isn't a moment to waste.
So if we keep on chugging along this way,
we'll wind up in the Massacre Forest?
The Murderous Forest.
And I'm pretty sure we're almost there.
The forest!
What happens next will depend
on what caused this destruction.
The monsters or our friends.
It's a mystery.
The ones who went ahead of us were
Director Bear, Heavy, Karios and Gores.
Oh, and Mishuel with his
big old dragon sword.
Yeah, I bet it was that last one I said.
Good thinking.
It makes sense.
Maybe he was slowing down the enemy.
Mishuel, did you stay behind all
alone to keep the enemy occupied?
Master Boxxo!
Oh, there he is.
Hello, Master.
I'm so happy you're safe.
I swear, I never stop believing in you.
Good work, Appalentant. Thanks, man.
Were you the ones who torched the forest?
I'm afraid so.
We had intended to buy
time via well-placed traps,
but then they were all
trampled by a giant monster.
Sadly, we had no choice but
to set the forest ablaze.
Uh, Mishuel, is that the royal
we or is someone with you?
My sister and her adorable friend showed
up just in the nick of time to help me out.
Hayachi! Usata! Usarion!
You can come out now!
It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
I'm exceedingly grateful for everything
you've done for my little brother.
These are my Essig friends.
Their names are Usata and Usarion.
I owe those two my life.
They rescued me after I happened
upon the Four-Fingered General.
Their swordsmanship is truly unmatched.
Or earmanship.
Amazing.
I can sense their great strength.
Form change!
Our posse's growing.
One truck's not enough.
And two's better than one anyway.
What?
The Netherlord's gone rogue?
So he's not doing the bidding
of the Demon Lord anymore?
That's correct.
The Netherlord used to
rule over the Demon Realm,
but he lost his throne to the current
Demon Lord and became his subject.
Didn't know that.
Sounds like a solid motivation
for betraying the Demon Lord.
On the upside, now we only have to
go ham on the Netherlord's army.
Our odds of winning this
just got a lot better.
Even still, it would be best if we could
join forces with the fortified city.
Too bad we have no way of
getting in touch with them.
Hmm.
I miss email.
Look, up in the air.
It's Kroyata!
Hello, old friend.
What brings you here?
I'm surprised you found us.
How's Kikoyu?
Oh, hey.
He's got a little birdie pouch.
It must be some kind of letter.
It is.
The Guardian has sent us an urgent update.
The Guardian?
So it's a letter from Field.
No, wait.
How does it make sense
that a Field can write?
I'll read it aloud.
Howdy, everyone.
My name is Field.
I heard the news from Director Bear,
so I'm up to date on the
nasty little sitch you're in.
I've already spoken with the Demon Lord,
so what do you say we all work together?
to kick the Nether Lord's evil butt?
He wants to kick butt?
That's one aggressive, um, Field.
I've included a detailed plan of
attack along with this here letter.
So please look it over carefully.
If you have any questions or concerns, just
jot them down and give them to Kuroyata.
Also, if you don't mind, please
show the following to Boxxo.
It's for you.
A vending machine's a weird
reincarnation, broseph.
But then again, I'm a
field, so I can't talk.
Let's have a nice long chat
about Japan when this is over.
I'd love to share some delicious veggies,
but I know you don't have a mouth.
Anyway, can't wait to meet ya!
Somehow, I have the feeling I'd
really hit it off with this field guy.
Whenever we meet, I'll gift him up
with some nostalgic Japanese goods.
After that, we held a strategy meeting.
We wrote down a few suggestions
and gave them to Kuro Yada.
Burning down the forest vanquished
quite a few of our monster foes.
Even so, we may have thinned the
ranks of the low-level monsters,
but nearly all of the highly
skilled ones still remain.
It's go time.
I'll do everything within my
vending powers to support our plan.
Besides, I'll get to fight alongside
my fellow countryman field.
Just the thought of it gets me excited.
Hey, Boxo, are you excited
about something? Huh?
Is she psychic now?
How can you tell?
Kind of seems like he's just
standing around like usual.
I guess you still haven't figured it out.
His lights are a dead
giveaway for when he's
going through something or feeling happy.
Even as a vending machine, my poker face
leaves a lot to be desired. He lights up.
Pity knows that.
It's obvious, kinda. Oh, Pity.
You're a shell-a-bad liar.
This isn't a competition or anything.
I've known Boxo the longest,
and I've spent the most time with
him, so I'm definitely the winner.
Then I'm the first runner-up.
Length of time doesn't matter.
If I were a lady, this is when I'd
say, don't fight over little old me.
But I'm not, so I won't.
Anyway, this is no time
to battle over Boxxo.
Right now, our only focus should
be kicking the Netherlord's butt!
Oh?
I look forward to serving you again.